var flashcards = 
    {
        "Lesson XX":
        [{"question": "Word: epithet",
          "answer": "a characterizing term"},
         {"question": "Word: abject",
          "answer": "miserable"},
         {"question": "Word: eccentric",
          "answer": "unconventional"},
         {"question": "Word: imperious",
          "answer": "overbearing"},
         {"question": "Word: solicitude",
          "answer": "concern"},
         {"question": "Word: genial",
          "answer": "kind"},
         {"question": "Word: stolid",
          "answer": "unemotional"},
         {"question": "Word: palpable",
          "answer": "touchable"},
         {"question": "Word: austere",
          "answer": "bare"},
         {"question": "Word: furtive",
          "answer": "stealthy"}],
        "Lesson XVIII":
        [{"question": "Word: adjacent",
          "answer": "adjoining"},
         {"question": "Word: transient",
          "answer": "existing briefly"},
         {"question": "Word: latent",
          "answer": "present but inactive"},
         {"question": "Word: livid",
          "answer": "bruised or pale"},
         {"question": "Word: censure",
          "answer": "strong criticism"},
         {"question": "Word: apprehension",
          "answer": "fear"},
         {"question": "Word: superfluous",
          "answer": "extra"},
         {"question": "Word: tangible",
          "answer": "touchable"},
         {"question": "Word: lurid",
          "answer": "sensational"},
         {"question": "Word: pervade",
          "answer": "spread throughout"}
        ],
        "Lesson XIX":
        [{"question": "Stem: punct\nModern examples: punctuate, punctual, punctilious",
          "answer": "point"},
         {"question": "Stem: trib\nModern examples: tribute, distribute, contribute",
          "answer": "pay"},
         {"question": "Stem: cap\nModern examples: capture, captivate, captious",
          "answer": "take"},
         {"question": "Stem: pond\nModern examples: ponder, preponderance, ponderous",
          "answer": "weight"},
         {"question": "Stem: rect\nModern examples: correct, rectilinear, rectitude",
          "answer": "right"},
         {"question": "Stem: geo\nModern examples: neothermal, geophysics, geosynchronous",
          "answer": "earth"},
         {"question": "Stem: scope\nModern examples: horoscope, electroscope, periscope",
          "answer": "look"},
         {"question": "Stem: anti\nModern examples: anticline, antibody, antitoxin",
          "answer": "against"},
         {"question": "Stem: intro\nModern examples: introduce, introspective, introvert",
          "answer": "into"},
         {"question": "Stem: neo\nModern examples: neologism, neoclassic, neonatal",
          "answer": "new"}],
        "Lesson XVII":
        [{"question": "Stem: per\nModern examples: percolate, peregrinate, perspicacity",
          "answer": "through"},
         {"question": "Stem: anim\nModern examples: animal, animadversion, magnanimous",
          "answer": "mind"},
         {"question": "Stem: tort\nModern examples: torturous, tortuous, retort",
          "answer": "twist"},
         {"question": "Stem: sanct\nModern examples: sacrosanct, sanctimonious, sanction",
          "answer": "holy"},
         {"question": "Stem: voc\nModern examples: vocal, invocation, vociferous",
          "answer": "voice"},
         {"question": "Stem: archy\nModern examples: Matriarch, patriarch, hierarchy",
          "answer": "government"},
         {"question": "Stem: bio\nModern examples: biogenesis, exobiology, biomorphic",
          "answer": "life"},
         {"question": "Stem: auto\nModern examples: automatic, automaton, autocracy",
          "answer": "self"},
         {"question": "Stem: chron\nModern examples: Chronometer, anachronism, chronic",
          "answer": "time"},
         {"question": "Stem: dec\nModern examples: decade, decagon, decathlon",
          "answer": "ten"}
        ],
        "Lesson XVI":
        [{"question": "Word: incongruous",
          "answer": "incompatible"},
         {"question": "Word: malevolence",
          "answer": "ill will"},
         {"question": "Word: ambiguous",
          "answer": "uncertain"},
         {"question": "Word: felicity",
          "answer": "great happiness"},
         {"question": "Word: irrevocable",
          "answer": "unalterable"},
         {"question": "Word: articulate",
          "answer": "express clearly"},
         {"question": "Word: vex",
          "answer": "to irritate"},
         {"question": "Word: prostrate",
          "answer": "lying down"},
         {"question": "Word: abyss",
          "answer": "bottomless depth"},
         {"question": "Word: martyr",
          "answer": "one who suffers"}
        ],
        "Lesson XV": 
        [
            {"question": "Stem: culp\nModern examples: culprit, culpable, exculpate",
             "answer": "blame"},
            {"question": "Stem: pugn\nModern examples: pugnacious, pugilist, oppugn",
             "answer": "fight"},
            {"question": "Stem: urb\nModern examples:urban, suburb, urbane",
             "answer": "city"},
            {"question": "Stem: numer\nModern examples: numeral, enumerate, supernumerary",
             "answer": "number"},
            {"question": "Stem: acr\nModern examples: acrid, acerbity, acrimony",
             "answer": "sharp"},
            {"question": "Stem: ject\nModern examples: subject, dejected, interjection",
             "answer": "throw"},
            {"question": "Stem: dorm\nModern examples: dormancy, dormitive, dormient",
             "answer": "sleep"},
            {"question": "Stem: magn\nModern examples: Magna Carta, magnum opus, magnanimous",
             "answer": "great"},
            {"question": "Stem: ver\nModern examples: aver, verisimilitude, veridical",
             "answer": "true"},
            {"question": "Stem: put\nModern examples: impute, computer, dispute",
             "answer": "think"}
        ],
        "Lesson XIV":
        [
            {"question": "Word: verdure",
             "answer": "vegetation"},
            {"question": "Word: equivocal",
             "answer": "ambiguous"},
            {"question": "Word: orthodox",
             "answer": "traditional"},
            {"question": "Word: profane",
             "answer": "irreverent"},
            {"question": "Word: tumult",
             "answer": "disturbance"},
            {"question": "Word: wistful",
             "answer": "yearning"},
            {"question": "Word: subtle",
             "answer": "slight"},
            {"question": "Word: sagacity",
             "answer": "wisdom"},
            {"question": "Word: remonstrate",
             "answer": "to object"},
            {"question": "Word: tedious",
             "answer": "boring"}
        ],
        "Lesson XIII":
        [{"question": "Stem: clud\nModern examples: exclude, included, preclude",
          "answer": "close"},
         {"question": "Stem: se\nModern examples: separate, secede, sedition",
          "answer": "apart"},
         {"question": "Stem: plu\nModern examples: plus, pluralism, nonplussed",
          "answer": "more"},
         {"question": "Stem: germ\nModern examples: germ, germinate, germane",
          "answer": "vital"},
         {"question": "Stem: fus\nModern examples: transfusion, infusion, fusillade",
          "answer": "pour"},
         {"question": "Stem: bene\nModern examples: beneficial, benevolent, benign",
          "answer": "good"},
         {"question": "Stem: son\nModern examples: consonant, resonant, assonance",
          "answer": "sound"},
         {"question": "Stem: nov\nModern examples: innovate, renovate, nova",
          "answer": "new"},
         {"question": "Stem: sangui\nModern examples: sanguine, sanguinary, consanguinity",
          "answer": "blood"},
         {"question": "Stem: cogn\nModern examples: recognize, cognomen, precognition",
          "answer": "know"}],
        "Lesson XII": [
            {"question": "Word: obsequious",
             "answer": "cringing, submissive"},
            {"question": "Word: ignominy",
             "answer": "disgrace"},
            {"question": "Word: acquiescence",
             "answer": "passive compliance"},
            {"question": "Word: impassive",
             "answer": "expressionless, without emotion"},
            {"question": "Word: impending",
             "answer": "about to happen"},
            {"question": "Word: vulgar",
             "answer": "common"},
            {"question": "Word: traverse",
             "answer": "to cross"},
            {"question": "Word: undulate",
             "answer": "to wave"},
            {"question": "Word: vivid",
             "answer": "bright"},
            {"question": "Word: pallor",
             "answer": "paleness"}
        ],
        "Lesson XI":
        [{"question": "Stem: grat\nModern examples: gratification, ingratiate, gratuitous",
          "answer": "pleasing"},
         {"question": "Stem: curr\nModern examples: current, recur, incur",
          "answer": "run"},
         {"question": "Stem: trans\nModern examples: transfer, transfusion, transcendent",
          "answer": "across"},
         {"question": "Stem: migr\nModern examples: migrate, migratory, transmigration",
          "answer": "wander"},
         {"question": "Stem: rupt\nModern examples: abrupt, corrupt, disrupt",
          "answer": "break"},
         {"question": "Stem: spec\nModern examples: specter, specious, spectrum",
          "answer": "look"},
         {"question": "Stem: pend\nModern examples: pending, impending, depend",
          "answer": "hang"},
         {"question": "Stem: omni\nModern examples: omnipotent, omnivorous, omniscient",
          "answer": "all"},
         {"question": "Stem: re\nModern examples: reiterate, regurgitate, revive",
          "answer": "again"},
         {"question": "Stem: ex\nModern examples: exculpate, exorbitant, except",
          "answer": "out"}],
        "Lesson X":
        [{"question": "Word: tacit",
          "answer": "unspoken"},
         {"question": "Word: affable",
          "answer": "friendly"},
         {"question": "Word: sanguine",
          "answer": "cheerfully confident"},
         {"question": "Word: torpid",
          "answer": "sluggish"},
         {"question": "Word: mortify",
          "answer": "profoundly humiliate"},
         {"question": "Word: melancholy",
          "answer": "sadness"},
         {"question": "Word: visage",
          "answer": "the face"},
         {"question": "Word: venerate",
          "answer": "to respect"},
         {"question": "Word: abate",
          "answer": "to lessen"},
         {"question": "Word: repose",
          "answer": "resting"}
        ],
        "Lesson IX":
        [{"question": "Stem: cred\nModern examples: credulous, credit, discredit",
          "answer": "believe"},
         {"question": "Stem: miss\nModern examples: missionary, missile, admission",
          "answer": "send"},
         {"question": "Stem: cide\nModern examples: genocide, herbicide, fungicide",
          "answer": "kill"},
         {"question": "Stem: dict\nModern examples: predict, dictionary, interdict",
          "answer": "say"},
         {"question": "Stem: bell\nModern examples: rebel, belligerence, casus belli",
          "answer": "war"},
         {"question": "Stem: mar\nModern examples: marine, maritime, mariner",
          "answer": "sea"},
         {"question": "Stem: junct\nModern examples: conjunction, junction, adjunct",
          "answer": "join"},
         {"question": "Stem: luc\nModern examples: lucidity, translucent, pellucid",
          "answer": "light"},
         {"question": "Stem: medi\nModern examples: medium, Mediterranean, in medias res",
          "answer": "middle"},
         {"question": "Stem: tempor\nModern examples: temporal, temporize, contemporary",
          "answer": "time"}
        ],
        "Lesson VII":
        [{"question": "Word: oblique",
          "answer": "indirect or slanting"},
         {"question": "Word: pensive",
          "answer": "thoughtful"},
         {"question": "Word: magnanimous",
          "answer": "generous"},
         {"question": "Word: importune",
          "answer": "to pester"},
         {"question": "Word: peremptory",
          "answer": "dictatorial"},
         {"question": "Word: placid",
          "answer": "calm"},
         {"question": "Word: singular",
          "answer": "unique"},
         {"question": "Word: amiable",
          "answer": "friendly"},
         {"question": "Word: incredulous",
          "answer": "skeptical"},
         {"question": "Word: perplex",
          "answer": "confuse"}],
        "Lesson VII":
        [{"question": "Stem: amat\nModern examples: amorous, amateur, amity",
          "answer": "love"},
         {"question": "Stem: luna\nModern examples: lunar, lunatic, sublunar",
          "answer": "moon"},
         {"question": "Stem: greg\nModern examples: congregate, segregate, gregarious",
          "answer": "group"},
         {"question": "Stem: clam\nModern examples: clamor, exclamation, declaim",
          "answer": "cry out"},
         {"question": "Stem: tang\nModern examples: tangle, tangent, intangible",
          "answer": "touch"},
         {"question": "Stem: aqua\nModern examples: aquifer, aquaplane, semiaquatic",
          "answer": "water"},
         {"question": "Stem: audi\nModern examples: audition, audiology, audit",
          "answer": "hear"},
         {"question": "Stem: scrib\nModern examples: transcribe, scribble, ascribe",
          "answer": "write"},
         {"question": "Stem: cede\nModern examples: antecedent, concede, intercede",
          "answer": "go"},
         {"question": "Stem: cise\nModern examples: precise, concise, decisive",
          "answer": "cut"},
        ],
        "Lesson VI":
        [{"question": "Word: ostentatious",
          "answer": "showy"},
         {"question": "Word: inexorable",
          "answer": "inevitable"},
         {"question": "Word: indolent",
          "answer": "lazy"},
         {"question": "Word: doleful",
          "answer": "mournful"},
         {"question": "Word: alacrity",
          "answer": "eagerness"},
         {"question": "Word: exquisite",
          "answer": "beautifully made"},
         {"question": "Word: clamor",
          "answer": "outcry"},
         {"question": "Word: sublime",
          "answer": "lofty"},
         {"question": "Word: tremulous",
          "answer": "quivering"},
         {"question": "Word: allude",
          "answer": "indirectly refer to"}
        ],
        "Lesson V":
        [{"question": "Stem: circum\nModern examples: circus, circumpolar, circumlocution",
          "answer": "around"},
         {"question": "Stem: mal\nModern examples: malcontent, malign, malapropism",
          "answer": "bad"},
         {"question": "Stem: post\nModern examples: postgraduate, posterior, postlude",
          "answer": "after"},
         {"question": "Stem: equi\nModern examples: equation, equinox, equitable",
          "answer": "equal"},
         {"question": "Stem: ante\nModern examples: antedate, ante meridiem, antepenult",
          "answer": "before"},
         {"question": "Stem: loco\nModern examples: locomotive, location, dislocate",
          "answer": "place"},
         {"question": "Stem: sur\nModern examples: surface, surrealist, surfeit",
          "answer": "over"},
         {"question": "Stem: alter\nModern examples: alteration, alternative, altruism",
          "answer": "other"},
         {"question": "Stem: contra\nModern examples: contradict, contrast, contrary",
          "answer": "against"},
         {"question": "Stem: stell\nModern examples: stellar, constellation, interstellar",
          "answer": "star"},
        ],
        "Lesson IV":
        [{"question": "Word: audible",
          "answer": "able to be heard"},
         {"question": "Word: benevolent",
          "answer": "charitable"},
         {"question": "Word: somber",
          "answer": "gloomy"},
         {"question": "Word: prostrate",
          "answer": "lying flat"},
         {"question": "Word: profuse",
          "answer": "abundant"},
         {"question": "Word: serene",
          "answer": "calm"},
         {"question": "Word: acute",
          "answer": "sharp"},
         {"question": "Word: grotesque",
          "answer": "distorted"},
         {"question": "Word: condescend",
          "answer": "to patronize"},
         {"question": "Word: odious",
          "answer": "hateful"}],
        "Lesson III":
        [{"question": "Stem: vita\nModern examples: vital, vitamin, revitalize",
          "answer": "life"},
         {"question": "Stem: vid\nModern examples: video, evidence, provide",
          "answer": "look"},
         {"question": "Stem: pater\nModern examples: paternal, patriarch, expatriate",
          "answer": "father"},
         {"question": "Stem: matri\nModern examples: maternal, matriarch, matrimony",
          "answer": "mother"},
         {"question": "Stem: pop\nModern examples: popular, population, populous",
          "answer": "people"},
         {"question": "Stem: un\nModern examples: unfit, unclear, unequaled",
          "answer": "not"},
         {"question": "Stem: inter\nModern examples: interstate, intermediary, interface",
          "answer": "between"},
         {"question": "Stem: semi\nModern examples: semitone, semilucid, semicircle",
          "answer": "half"},
         {"question": "Stem: dis\nModern examples: dispute, dissonant, dissuade",
          "answer": "away"},
         {"question": "Stem: sym\nModern examples: symbol, symposium, symbiosis",
          "answer": "together"}
        ],
        "Lesson II":
        [{"question": "Word: placate",
          "answer": "to appease"},
         {"question": "Word: derision",
          "answer": "ridicule"},
         {"question": "Word: vivacious",
          "answer": "full of life"},
         {"question": "Word: procure",
          "answer": "to acquire"},
         {"question": "Word: retort",
          "answer": "a quick, clever reply"},
         {"question": "Word: countenance",
          "answer": "facial expression"},
         {"question": "Word: profound",
          "answer": "deep"},
         {"question": "Word: manifest",
          "answer": "obvious"},
         {"question": "Word: prodigious",
          "answer": "huge"},
         {"question": "Word: languor",
          "answer": "weakness"}],
        "Lesson I": 
        [{"question": "Stem: bi\nModern examples: binocular, bilingual, binary",
          "answer": "two"},
         {"question": "Stem: sub\nModern examples: subterranean, subordinate, submit",
          "answer": "under"},
         {"question": "Stem: de\nModern examples: deduct, demolish, denounce",
          "answer": "down"},
         {"question": "Stem: pre\nModern examples: preposition, precede, predecessor",
          "answer": "before"},
         {"question": "Stem: super\nModern examples: superfluous, supernatural, supercilious",
          "answer": "over"},
         {"question": "Stem: com\nModern examples: combine, complete, complex",
          "answer": "together"},
         {"question": "Stem: intra\nModern examples: intramural, intracellular, intravenous",
          "answer": "within"},
         {"question": "Stem: cent\nModern examples: century, centimeter, centurion",
          "answer": "one hundred"},
         {"question": "Stem: ad\nModern examples: adhere, adapt, advocate",
          "answer": "to"},
         {"question": "Stem: fer\nModern examples: transfer, aquifer, conifer",
          "answer": "carry"}
        ]
    };
